Contact

Ananta kr ghosh,190,Rakhal ghosh rd.,P.O:Rajur,kolkata-700149 8017026826 (Home) ghosh7ananta@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/anantakumar-ghosh-08583311b (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

html

css

Responsive Web Design

Ananta kumar Ghosh

Visiting Researcher at Indian Statistics institute,kolkata Budge Budge-I

Summary

I am a web developer with 5+ years of experience in PHP and Python Development. I have a sound knowledge over HTML 5,CSS 3,bootstrap 4,javascript,jquery ,python3, python2 , MySQL, wordpress, laravel, codeigniter, Django with rest API.I am capable to develop a CMS website Web applications etc. If you give me your work I will not disappoint you and my work will low price and high profesonal. And all projects are negotiable on money.

Experience

Indian Statistics institute,kolkata Visiting Researcher January 2020 - Present (8 months) Kolkata, West Bengal, India

Self-Employed Web Developer February 2016 - Present (4 years 7 months)

Self-Employed Computer Teacher May 2016 - May 2020 (4 years 1 month) bhangar

Bargaad software solutions pvt. Itd Web Designer August 2019 - September 2019 (2 months) Kolkata Area, India

Education

West Bengal University of Technology, Kolkata B.Tech, Computer science and technology · (2012 - 2016)